Educational Technology Services Records UA245
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Great Courses, 2014 -- 2017; UA245.001; 626 Digital Object(s); 1 Web sites
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 9 -- Descartes' Principia: The Vortex Theory of the Heavens -- Part 9., 2014-10-28; gc.phil167.502
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 9, Part 9.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 9 -- Descartes' Principia: The Vortex Theory of the Heavens -- Part 10., 2014-10-28; gc.phil167.503
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 9, Part 10.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 9 -- Descartes' Principia: The Vortex Theory of the Heavens -- Part 11 - Part 12., 2014-10-28; gc.phil167.504
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 9, Part 11 - 12.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 9 -- Descartes' Principia: The Vortex Theory of the Heavens -- Part 13., 2014-10-28; gc.phil167.505
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 9, Part 13.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 9 -- Descartes' Principia: The Vortex Theory of the Heavens -- Part 14., 2014-10-28; gc.phil167.506
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 9, Part 14.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 10 -- Huygens and the Beginnings of Rational Mechanics -- Complete., 2014-11-04; gc.phil167.507
    Section: Class 10, Complete.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 10 -- Huygens and the Beginnings of Rational Mechanics -- Part 1 - Part 2., 2014-11-04; gc.phil167.508
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 10, Part 1 - 2.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 10 -- Huygens and the Beginnings of Rational Mechanics -- Part 3., 2014-11-04; gc.phil167.509
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 10, Part 3.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 10 -- Huygens and the Beginnings of Rational Mechanics -- Part 4., 2014-11-04; gc.phil167.510
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 10, Part 4.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 10 -- Huygens and the Beginnings of Rational Mechanics -- Part 5., 2014-11-04; gc.phil167.511
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 10, Part 5.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 10 -- Huygens and the Beginnings of Rational Mechanics -- Part 6., 2014-11-04; gc.phil167.512
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 10, Part 6.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 10 -- Huygens and the Beginnings of Rational Mechanics -- Part 7., 2014-11-04; gc.phil167.513
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 10, Part 7.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 10 -- Huygens and the Beginnings of Rational Mechanics -- Part 8., 2014-11-04; gc.phil167.514
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 10, Part 8.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 10 -- Huygens and the Beginnings of Rational Mechanics -- Part 9., 2014-11-04; gc.phil167.515
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 10, Part 9.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 10 -- Huygens and the Beginnings of Rational Mechanics -- Part 10., 2014-11-04; gc.phil167.516
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 10, Part 10.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 10 -- Huygens and the Beginnings of Rational Mechanics -- Part 11., 2014-11-04; gc.phil167.517
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 10, Part 11.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 10 -- Huygens and the Beginnings of Rational Mechanics -- Part 12., 2014-11-04; gc.phil167.518
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 10, Part 12.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 10 -- Huygens and the Beginnings of Rational Mechanics -- Part 13., 2014-11-04; gc.phil167.519
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 10, Part 13.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 10 -- Huygens and the Beginnings of Rational Mechanics -- Part 14., 2014-11-04; gc.phil167.520
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 10, Part 14.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 10 -- Huygens and the Beginnings of Rational Mechanics -- Part 15., 2014-11-04; gc.phil167.521
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 10, Part 15.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 11 -- Other Developments in Astronomy from 1642 to 1684 -- Complete., 2014-11-18; gc.phil167.522
    Section: Class 11, Complete.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 11 -- Other Developments in Astronomy from 1642 to 1684 -- Part 1., 2014-11-18; gc.phil167.523
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 11, Part 1.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 11 -- Other Developments in Astronomy from 1642 to 1684 -- Part 2., 2014-11-18; gc.phil167.524
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 11, Part 2.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 11 -- Other Developments in Astronomy from 1642 to 1684 -- Part 3., 2014-11-18; gc.phil167.525
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 11, Part 3.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 11 -- Other Developments in Astronomy from 1642 to 1684 -- Part 4., 2014-11-18; gc.phil167.526
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 11, Part 4.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 11 -- Other Developments in Astronomy from 1642 to 1684 -- Part 5., 2014-11-18; gc.phil167.527
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 11, Part 5.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 11 -- Other Developments in Astronomy from 1642 to 1684 -- Part 6., 2014-11-18; gc.phil167.528
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 11, Part 6.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 11 -- Other Developments in Astronomy from 1642 to 1684 -- Part 7., 2014-11-18; gc.phil167.529
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 11, Part 7.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 11 -- Other Developments in Astronomy from 1642 to 1684 -- Part 8., 2014-11-18; gc.phil167.530
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 11, Part 8.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 11 -- Other Developments in Astronomy from 1642 to 1684 -- Part 9., 2014-11-18; gc.phil167.531
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 11, Part 9.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 11 -- Other Developments in Astronomy from 1642 to 1684 -- Part 10., 2014-11-18; gc.phil167.532
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 11, Part 10.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 11 -- Other Developments in Astronomy from 1642 to 1684 -- Part 11., 2014-11-18; gc.phil167.533
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 11, Part 11.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 11 -- Other Developments in Astronomy from 1642 to 1684 -- Part 12., 2014-11-18; gc.phil167.534
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 11, Part 12.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 11 -- Other Developments in Astronomy from 1642 to 1684 -- Part 13., 2014-11-18; gc.phil167.535
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 11, Part 13.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 11 -- Other Developments in Astronomy from 1642 to 1684 -- Part 14., 2014-11-18; gc.phil167.536
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 11, Part 14.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 11 -- Other Developments in Astronomy from 1642 to 1684 -- Part 15., 2014-11-18; gc.phil167.537
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 11, Part 15.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 12 -- Newton's Early Unpublished Work in Mechanics -- Complete., 2014-11-25; gc.phil167.538
    Section: Class 12, Complete.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 12 -- Newton's Early Unpublished Work in Mechanics -- Part 1., 2014-11-25; gc.phil167.539
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 12, Part 1.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 12 -- Newton's Early Unpublished Work in Mechanics -- Part 2., 2014-11-25; gc.phil167.540
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 12, Part 2.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 12 -- Newton's Early Unpublished Work in Mechanics -- Part 3., 2014-11-25; gc.phil167.541
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 12, Part 3.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 12 -- Newton's Early Unpublished Work in Mechanics -- Part 4., 2014-11-25; gc.phil167.542
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 12, Part 4.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 12 -- Newton's Early Unpublished Work in Mechanics -- Part 5., 2014-11-25; gc.phil167.543
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 12, Part 5.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 12 -- Newton's Early Unpublished Work in Mechanics -- Part 6 - Part 7., 2014-11-25; gc.phil167.544
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 12, Part 6 - 7.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 12 -- Newton's Early Unpublished Work in Mechanics -- Part 8., 2014-11-25; gc.phil167.545
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 12, Part 8.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 12 -- Newton's Early Unpublished Work in Mechanics -- Part 9., 2014-11-25; gc.phil167.546
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 12, Part 9.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 12 -- Newton's Early Unpublished Work in Mechanics -- Part 10., 2014-11-25; gc.phil167.547
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 12, Part 10.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 12 -- Newton's Early Unpublished Work in Mechanics -- Part 11., 2014-11-25; gc.phil167.548
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 12, Part 11.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 12 -- Newton's Early Unpublished Work in Mechanics -- Part 12., 2014-11-25; gc.phil167.549
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 12, Part 12.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 12 -- Newton's Early Unpublished Work in Mechanics -- Part 13., 2014-11-25; gc.phil167.550
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 12, Part 13.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 13 -- Newton's De Motu Corporum in Gyrum (i.e. Version 1) -- Complete., 2014-12-02; gc.phil167.551
    Section: Class 13, Complete.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 13 -- Newton's De Motu Corporum in Gyrum (i.e. Version 1) -- Part 1., 2014-12-02; gc.phil167.552
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 13, Part 1.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 13 -- Newton's De Motu Corporum in Gyrum (i.e. Version 1) -- Part 2., 2014-12-02; gc.phil167.553
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 13, Part 2.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 13 -- Newton's De Motu Corporum in Gyrum (i.e. Version 1) -- Part 3., 2014-12-02; gc.phil167.554
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 13, Part 3.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 13 -- Newton's De Motu Corporum in Gyrum (i.e. Version 1) -- Part 4., 2014-12-02; gc.phil167.555
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 13, Part 4.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 13 -- Newton's De Motu Corporum in Gyrum (i.e. Version 1) -- Part 5., 2014-12-02; gc.phil167.556
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 13, Part 5.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 13 -- Newton's De Motu Corporum in Gyrum (i.e. Version 1) -- Part 6., 2014-12-02; gc.phil167.557
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 13, Part 6.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 13 -- Newton's De Motu Corporum in Gyrum (i.e. Version 1) -- Part 7., 2014-12-02; gc.phil167.558
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 13, Part 7.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 13 -- Newton's De Motu Corporum in Gyrum (i.e. Version 1) -- Part 8., 2014-12-02; gc.phil167.559
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 13, Part 8.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 13 -- Newton's De Motu Corporum in Gyrum (i.e. Version 1) -- Part 9., 2014-12-02; gc.phil167.560
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 13, Part 9.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 13 -- Newton's De Motu Corporum in Gyrum (i.e. Version 1) -- Part 10., 2014-12-02; gc.phil167.561
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 13, Part 10.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 13 -- Newton's De Motu Corporum in Gyrum (i.e. Version 1) -- Part 11., 2014-12-02; gc.phil167.562
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 13, Part 11.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 13 -- Newton's De Motu Corporum in Gyrum (i.e. Version 1) -- Part 12., 2014-12-02; gc.phil167.563
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 13, Part 12.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 13 -- Newton's De Motu Corporum in Gyrum (i.e. Version 1) -- Part 13., 2014-12-02; gc.phil167.564
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 13, Part 13.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 13 -- Newton's De Motu Corporum in Gyrum (i.e. Version 1) -- Part 14., 2014-12-02; gc.phil167.565
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 13, Part 14.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 13 -- Newton's De Motu Corporum in Gyrum (i.e. Version 1) -- Part 15., 2014-12-02; gc.phil167.566
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 13, Part 15.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 13 -- Newton's De Motu Corporum in Gyrum (i.e. Version 1) -- Part 16., 2014-12-02; gc.phil167.567
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 13, Part 16.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 14 -- Newton's De Motu Corporum, Version 3 -- Complete., 2014-12-09; gc.phil167.568
    Section: Class 14, Complete.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 14 -- Newton's De Motu Corporum, Version 3 -- Part 1., 2014-12-09; gc.phil167.569
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 14, Part 1.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 14 -- Newton's De Motu Corporum, Version 3 -- Part 2., 2014-12-09; gc.phil167.570
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 14, Part 2.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 14 -- Newton's De Motu Corporum, Version 3 -- Part 3., 2014-12-09; gc.phil167.571
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 14, Part 3.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 14 -- Newton's De Motu Corporum, Version 3 -- Part 4., 2014-12-09; gc.phil167.572
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 14, Part 4.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 14 -- Newton's De Motu Corporum, Version 3 -- Part 5., 2014-12-09; gc.phil167.573
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 14, Part 5.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 14 -- Newton's De Motu Corporum, Version 3 -- Part 6., 2014-12-09; gc.phil167.574
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 14, Part 6.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 14 -- Newton's De Motu Corporum, Version 3 -- Part 7., 2014-12-09; gc.phil167.575
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 14, Part 7.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 14 -- Newton's De Motu Corporum, Version 3 -- Part 8., 2014-12-09; gc.phil167.576
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 14, Part 8.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 14 -- Newton's De Motu Corporum, Version 3 -- Part 9., 2014-12-09; gc.phil167.577
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 14, Part 9.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 14 -- Newton's De Motu Corporum, Version 3 -- Part 10., 2014-12-09; gc.phil167.578
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 14, Part 10.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 14 -- Newton's De Motu Corporum, Version 3 -- Part 11., 2014-12-09; gc.phil167.579
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 14, Part 11.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 14 -- Newton's De Motu Corporum, Version 3 -- Part 12., 2014-12-09; gc.phil167.580
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 14, Part 12.
  - Slides to Philosophy 167: Class 14 -- Newton's De Motu Corporum, Version 3 -- Part 13., 2014-12-09; gc.phil167.581
    Generally corresponds to the video segment: Class 14, Part 13.
  - Syllabus to Philosophy 167: Science Before Newton's PRINCIPIA., 2014-09-01; gc.phil167.582
    Entire course syllabus which provides the outline and expectations of the course.
  - Tufts Great Courses web crawl, 2017; UA245.001.00001; 1 Web sites Web site as crawled on December 6, 2017.
    The webiste is available to Tufts Community users only. Non-Tufts users may request access using 'add to list.'